https://bergenstrahle.se/integritetspolicy-anvandning-av-cookies/

Privacy policy & cookie use
At Bergenstråhle & Partners, we’re committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Here we explain when and why we collect personal information about people who visit our websites, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure. We may change this Policy from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you’re agreeing to be bound by this Policy. Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices should be sent by email to info@bergenstrahle.se or by writing to Bergenstråhle & Partners Stockholm AB, P.O. Box 17704, SE-118 93 Stockholm, Sweden.
Who is Bergenstråhle & Partners?
Bergenstråhle was founded in 1934 and is one of Sweden’s most innovative IP consultancy businesses. We are based in four major Swedish engineering and entrepreneurial hotspots and have our own authorized patent agents for Europe, China and the United States.
How do we collect information?
We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us about services, if you register to receive our thought leadership materials (e.g. eBooks, Whitepapers, Webinars, etc.) newsletters, visit our events or when we work with you as our client either directly or through a partner.
What type of information is collected?
We may collect the following information:
Name and job title.
Contact information including email address.
IP address, and information regarding what pages are accessed.
We might ask you to provide more information when using certain parts of this website or when you e.g. download thought leadership material. In that case you can be assured that it will be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
What are we doing with the information we gather?
The bases we use for the processing of your data is legitimate interests. That’s because your interactions with our company and website tells us that you might be interested in our services. Therefor we believe that the content we provide will help your business become even more successful.
We may use your information to:
Send you our thought leadership-material, newsletter, or invite you to events if the content is going to be relevant to you. Each email will include a simple unsubscribe link for you to opt out if you wish.
To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into by you and us.
Use re-marketing across trusted websites, including Google Ads.
Use your details to target relevant ads to you on social media channels, including; LinkedIn, Instagram and Twitter.
Seek your views or comments on the services we provide.
Notify you of changes to our services.
Send you communications which you have requested and that may be of interest to you. We review our retention periods for personal information on a regular basis. We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as its necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as its set out in any relevant contract you hold with us. If you unsubscribe from, for example a newsletter, we may retain your data on a suppression list to ensure you do not receive future email communications.
Analyse behaviour with the goal of optimising our solutions and platforms. Doing debug and analyze trends and statistics in usage.
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties.
Access to your information?
Third Party Service Providers working on our behalf: We may pass your information to our third party service providers (such as Hubspot), agents, subcontractors and other associated organizations for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf. However, when we use third party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the service and we have a contract in place that requires them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own direct marketing purposes. Please be reassured that we will not release your information to third parties beyond the Bergenstråhle network for them to use for their own direct marketing purposes, unless you have requested us to do so, or we are required to do so by law, for example, by a court order or for the purpose of preventing of fraud or other crime. Third Party Product Providers we work in association with: We work closely with third party product providers to bring you a range of quality and reliable services. When you enquire about or purchase one or more of these services, the relevant third party product provider will use your details to provide you with information and carry out their obligations arising from any contracts you have entered into with them. In some cases, they will be acting as a data controller of your information and therefore we advise you to read their Privacy Policy. These third party product providers will share your information with us which we will use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Your choices
You have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive direct marketing communications from us about our services, then you can use the unsubscribe link in each email communication or contact us by email to info@bergenstrahle.se to be removed.
We will not contact you for marketing purposes by email, phone or text message unless you have given your prior consent or we believe that there is a legitimate interest. We will not contact you for marketing purposes by post if you have indicated that you do not wish to be contacted. You can change your marketing preferences at any time by contacting us by email: info@bergenstrahle.se
Update and access your information
The accuracy of your information is important to us. If you change email address, or any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please email us at: info@bergenstrahle.se, or write to us at: Bergenstråhle & Partners Stockholm AB, P.O. Box 17704, SE-118 93 Stockholm, Sweden. You have the right to ask for a copy of the information Bergenstråhle hold about you. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Security precautions in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of your information
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.
Non-sensitive details (your email address etc.) are transmitted normally over the Internet, and this can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Profiling
We may analyse your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of additional information about you when it is available from external sources to help us do this effectively. We may also use your personal information to detect and reduce fraud and credit risk.
Use of ”cookies”
Like most other websites, bergenstrahle.se and its subsidiaries use Cookies across our websites to improve your user experience.
User Agreement
By continuing to use our site, you agree to the placement of cookies on your device. You can manage the cookies stored on your computer, or turn them off completely, through your browser settings. Be aware that this may affect your browsing experience or even prevent you from using certain services such as those with a secure login, which require cookies to be set in order to work.
We use first-party Google Analytics cookies to track anonymous usage statistics and do not collect any personal information that can be used to identify you. This helps Bergenstrahle to analyse data about webpage usage and improve our website in order to tailor it to our visitors interest. Google Analytics stores information about what pages you visit, how long you are on the site, how you got here and what you click on.
To operate our sites we also use “session cookies”. These cookies are used to remember selections and preferences that you’ve already made or information that you’ve already given. Certain parts of our sites will not work if cookies cannot be set (for example if you set your browser to refuse all cookies).
On some parts of our site we allow you to easily share pages and post them to social networks. These social media buttons usually use third party cookies. For more information about how to manage cookies and their uses visit About Cookies.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
16 or under
We are concerned to protect the privacy of children aged 16 or under. If you are aged 16 or under‚ please get your parent/guardian’s permission beforehand whenever you provide us with personal information.
Transferring your information outside of Europe
As part of the services offered to you, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (“EU”). These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the European countries and the UK. By submitting your personal data, you’re agreeing to this transfer, storing or processing. If we transfer your information outside of the EU or the UK in this way, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected as outlined in this Policy. If you use our services while you are outside the EU and the UK, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide you with those services.
Review of this Policy
We keep this Policy under regular review. We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by placing a prominent notice on our website.
This Policy was last updated in September 2018.
Information
Säkerhet
Integritetspolicy & användning av cookies
GDPR
Bergenstråhle är föregångare inom området immaterialrätt sedan starten 1934. Vi är en fullservicebyrå som hjälper våra kunder med rådgivning, att identifiera och skapa immateriella tillgångar, hantera immaterialrättsportföljer och kommersialisera tillgångar och rättigheter. Framförallt är vi pionjärer när det gäller att tillföra affärsvärde genom strategier och processer som möjliggör Return-On-Innovation®.
Följ oss
@ 2020 Bergenstråhle & Partners. All rights reserved.
